Guide to the History of Education Society collection, 1960-2013 MS2341
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Governance and Society records, 1960-2006; Series 2
  - Correspondence Professor Clarence Karler, May 25, 1978; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence between Ellen Condliffe Lagemann and Robin Berson, October 4, 1984; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence between Fiona Tipple and Robin Berson, 1985; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson an dMr. James R. Groves, 1967; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence between Professor Henry Perkinson and Dr. Ezri Atzmon, December 5, 1968; September 12, 1969; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Journal of Modern History, May 3, 1967; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence between James Hecimovich and Paul H. Mattingly, 1980; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence between Jennings L. Wagoner and Robin Berson, December 23, 1983; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence between Joshua Weinstein and Joan N. Burstyn, 1985; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence between Julius A. Elias and Henry J. Perkinson, May 5, 1967; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence between Laurence Veysey, June 24, 1976; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence between Lillian Weber and Paul H. Mattingly, June 21, 1973; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Correspondences between Professor Marvin Lazerson, January 25, 1977; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence between Mike Lybarger and Robin Berson, February 8, 1984; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence between N. Stockdale and Robin Berson, February 14, 1985; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence between Neil Sutherland and Professor Carl F. Kaestle, April 16, 1981; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence between Neil Sutherland and Henry J. Perkinson, December 19, 1968; January 6, 1969; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence between Neil Sutherland and Dr. Jim Wallace, September 17, 1981; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence between Neil Sutherland and Professor Carl Kaestle, September 19, 1981; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence between Neil Sutherland and Dr. Marvin Lazerson, September 17, 1981; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence between Neil Sutherland and Paul H. Mattingly, October 29, 1982; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence between Neil Sutherland and Paul H. Mattingly, March 20, 1973; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence between Neil Sutherland and Paul H. Mattingly, April 2, 1975; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence between Neil Sutherland and Paul H. Mattingly, September 20, 1976; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence between Neil Sutherland and Paul H. Mattingly and Michael, March 13, 1975; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence between Orville T. Murphy and Allan Horlick, 1974; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence between Otis A. Singletary and Henry J. Perkinson, November 1967; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence between Patricia Albjerg Graham and Professor Charles Burgess, August 27, 1971; October 10, 1972; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence between Patricia Albjerg and colleagues, September 22, 1972; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence between Patricia Albjerg Graham and Prof. Ezri etc., February 5, 1973; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence between Patricia Albjerg Graham and members of the Board of Directors of the History of Education, November 1972; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Sister Alice, 1974; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Sister Alice Tobriner, 1973; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Ann Keppel, November 24, 1976-January 3, 1977; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Bayrd Still, November 17, 1975; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Bernard J. Looks, December 6, 1972; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Bernard J. Looks, 1973; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Brian Wilson, December 7, 1972; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Charles Burgess, 1977; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Mr. Bruce Kuklick, October 7, 1976; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Profs. Charles Burgess and David Tyack, 1983; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and C. B. Schmitt, June 14, 1974; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Charles Tilly, March 24, 1972; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Charles Tilly, September 7, 1971; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Charles Tilly, May 3, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Charles Tilly, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Charles Tilly, May 8, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Charles Tilly, September 25, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Charles Webster, January 9, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor David Almendinger, June 26, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and David C. Humphrey, January 12, 1971; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and David C. Humphrey, July 11, 1971; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and David C. Humphrey, June 27, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and David C. Humphrey, March 6, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and David C. Humphrey, May 31, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and David C. Humphrey, July 2, 1980; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and educational studies, January 19, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Elyse S. Fleming, October 16, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor Flanagan, June 1978; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor Geraldine Jonich clifford, November 26, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor Geraldine J. Clifford, August 30, 1976; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor Geraldine Clifford, October 7, 1976; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor Geraldine J. Clifford, May 26, 1977; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor Geraldine J. Clifford, July 13, 1977; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Harold Silver, 1976-1978; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and head, December 16, 1968; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Henry C. Johnson, Jr., October 6, 1981; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and History of Education Society Board of Directors, February 18, 1982; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Hope Smith, 1978; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Jean Jacques Waardenburg, 1975; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Jean A Scott, 1980; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Jaime Suchlicki, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and James D. Anderson, 1977; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and James John, November 9, 1971; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and James John, July 2, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and James John, June 5, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Mrs. Jane K. Parker, January 22, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Jennings Wagnor Jr., March 1978; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Joan Burstyn, 1976-1977; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Joel Spring, May 17, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Joel Spring, July 25, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and John Barker, 1974-1975; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and John Hendrick Clarke, 1975-1976, 1978; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and John E. Talbott, December 16, 1970; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and John E. Talbott, November 12, 1971; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and John E. Talbott, March 14, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and John E. Talbott, August 1, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and John E. Talbott, January 18, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and John H. Weiss, January 16, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and John H. Weiss, April 2, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and John H. Weiss, October 6, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and John H. Weiss, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Journal of Social History, 1967, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Journal of Higher Education, March 11, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Journal of Higher Education, May 30, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Journal of Higher Education, October 7, 1976; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Jurgen H. Herbst, 1973-1974, 1978; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor K. Charlton, February 11, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Dr. Keith Hoskin, February 3, 1983; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Keith A. McLeod, 1977, 1978; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Laurence Veysey, April 9, 1969; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Laurence Veysey, April 25, 1969; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Laurence Veysey, September 23, 1969; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Laurence Veysey, July 1, 1976; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Laurence Veysey, October 20, 1971; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Laurence Veysey, 1970; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Laurence Veysey, July 2, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Laurence Veysey, March 29, 1976; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Laurence Veysey, April 30, 1976; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Lillian Weber, May 8, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Lloyd deMause, July 20, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and, August 31, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Mrs. Louise Tilly, July 13, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Louise Tilly, September 13, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Louise Tilly, June 5, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Ludwig F. Schaefer, Undated; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor Maris Vinovskis, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Mark Beach, 1977; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Mr. Martin Sullivan, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Marvin Lazerson, 1973, 1975; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Mr. Michael Katz, September 25, 1975; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Persis Hunt, November 13, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Persis Hunt, September 1, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Phyllis Dain, 1974-1975; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Polska Akademi Nauk, April 14, 1975; March 16, 1976; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Prof. P Stevens, 1971, 1973, 1975; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Phyllis Stock, September 20, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor R. Jackson Wilson, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Ray B. Browne, June 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor Ray Jobling, June 4, 1971; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Ray Yarborough, 1975, 1976; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor R. Robling, June 5, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor R. G. Jobling, July 4, 1971; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor R. G. Jobling, October 20, 1971; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor R. G. Jobling, December 1, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 92)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor R. G. Jobling, July 2, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Richard Lee Huff, June 27, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Robert J. Taggart, 1975; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Robert Tignor, June 29, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Robert Tignor, July 12, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 97)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Robert Wellman, October 23, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 98)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Robert P. Wolff, May 8, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 99)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Saint Louis University, November 1, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Selwyn K. Troen, 1974-1978; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 101)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Sheldon Rothblatt, 1978; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 102)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Sociology of Education, June 7, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 103)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Dr. Marilyn Tobias, November 17, 1977; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 104)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Trevor Wigney, February 22, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Trevor J. Wigney, April 20, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 106)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Trevor Wigney, May 3, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Trevor Wigney, July 2, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 108)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Rena L. Vassar, December 11, 1970; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 109)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Rena L. Vassar, November 9, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 110)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Selwyn K. Troen, July 3, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 111)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Selwyn K. Troen, July 18, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 112)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Professor William Johnson, June 26, 1974; July 10, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 113)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and William Johnson, July 10, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 114)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and William H. Jordy, October 6, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 115)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and William Margolin, November 20, 1984; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 116)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and William Reddy, 1978; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 117)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Wilson Smith, May 17, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 118)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Wilson Smith, September 12, 1972; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 119)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Wilson Smith, June 27, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 120)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Wilson Smith, July 3, 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 121)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Wilson Smith, June 5, 1974; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 122)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Winton Solberg, June 28, 1977; 1978; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 123)
  - Correspondence between Paul H. Mattingly and Winton Solberg, June 28, 1977; 1978; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 123)
  - Correspondence between Paul Nash and Frank Russo, June 28, 1966; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence between Paul Nash and Perk, October 1967; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence between Paul Nash and Walter Feinberg, June 28, 1966; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence between Persis Hunt and Paul H. Mattingly, September 18, 1972; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence between Persis Hunt and Paul H. Mattingly, November 3, 1972; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence between Philip West and Paul H. Mattingly, 1970-1972; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence between Phyllis Stock and Paul H. Mattingly, September 15, 1972; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence between Pierre H. Laurent and colleagues, 1972; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence between R. G. Jobling and Paul H. Mattingly, June 24, 1971; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence between R. G. Jobling and Paul H. Mattingly, August 5, 1971; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence between R. G. Jobling and Paul H. Mattingly, October 25, 1971; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence between R. L. Plancke and Henry J. Perkinson, April 1967; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence between Raul Vargas Vega and History of Education Quarterly, 1972; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence between Ray B. Browne and Paul H. Mattingly, July 5, 1973; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence between Mr. Ray Kumar and HES, January 31, 1968; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence between Reed Veda and Paul H. Mattingly, October 14, 1984; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence between Rena Foy and Professor David Tyack, November 18, 1968; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence between Richard J. Altenbaugh and Professor Sol Cohen, May 10, 1982; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence between Richard A. McKee and Paul H. Mattingly, June 5, 1974; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence between Richard C. Rose to History of Education Quarterly, June 21, 1977; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence between Richard C. Rose and Paul H. Mattingly, November 23, 1976; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence between Richard J. Altenbaugh and Professor Sol Cohen, May 10, 1982; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence between Richard W. Dougherty and Paul Mattingly, June 24, 1974; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence between Richard Lee Huff and Allan S. Horlick, April 12, 1973; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence between Richard G. Lyons and Henry J. Perkinson, 1966, 1967; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence between Richard K. Seckinger and colleague, January 11, 1965; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence between W. Richard Stephens and Professor David B. Tyack, October 29, 1969; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence between Robert H. Beck and Henry J. Perkinson, 1966; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence between Robert E. Potter and Dr. Ezri Atzmon, November 20, 1969; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence between Robert Reilly and Dr. Ezri Atzmon, March 9, 1971; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence between Robert F. Richards and Mr. Henry J. Perkinson, December 27, 1967; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence between Robert L. Tignor and Paul H. Mattingly, July 7, 1973; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence between Robert R. Wellman and Paul H. Mattingly, Undated; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence between Robert R. Wellman and Paul H. Mattingly, October 26, 1973; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence between Robert P. Wolff and Paul H. Mattingly, May 18, 1973; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence between Roberta Frankfurt and Douglas Myers, 1977; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence between Roberta Wien and Dr. B. Bessant, December 11, 1974; February 9, 1975; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence between Roberta Wien and Assistant to the Editor, Intellectual Digest, 1971, 1974; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence between Roberta Wien and K. S. Pickens, 1973; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence between Roberta Wien and Centro de Information Cientifica y Tecnica, Universidad de la Habana, 1973; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence between Roberta Wien and Scuola e Citta La Nuova Italie, 1974; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Alfred Lauterman, August 30, 1979; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Alice T. Friedman, June 10, 1985; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and American Journal of Education, October 1, 1980; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Annette Duggan, June 4, 1980; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 45)